(Leoanard:)If future Biff
goes back to 2015
(Leoanard:)right after he gives
young Biff the almanac,
(Leoanard:)he could get back to the 2015
with Marty and Doc in it.
(Leoanard:)Because it wasn't until
his 21st birthday
(Leoanard:)that 1955 Biff
placed his first bet.
SHELDON:
Wait. Whoa, whoa.
Is "placed" right?
(Leonard:)What do you mean?
Is "placed" the right tense
(Sheldon:)for something that would have
happened in the future
(Sheldon:)of a past that was affected
by something from the future?
(Leonard:)Had will have placed?
(Sheldon:)That's my boy.
(Leonard:)Okay, so, it wasn't until
his 21st birthday
(Leonard:)that Biff had will have
placed his first bet
(Leonard:)and made his millions.
(Leonard:)That's when
he altered the timeline.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, but he had will
haven't placed it!
What?!
Unlike Hot Tub Time Machine,
(Sheldon:)this couldn't be more simple.
(Sheldon:)When Biff gets the almanac
in 1955,
(Sheldon:)the alternate future
he creates isn't the one